A Guide to the Addison D. Campbell papers, 1948-1994
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Addison D. Campbell papers, 1948-1994
The Library of Virginia
36464
15 cu. ft. and 33 boxes and 7 folders
Addison D. Campbell
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Addison D. Campbell of Richmond, Virginia.
Biographical Information
Addison D. Campbell of Henrico County, Virginia, was active in the Henrico County Democratic Party and served on the Henrico County Democratic Committee. He taught physics at the University of Richmond.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1948-1994, of Addison D. Campbell of Henrico County, Virginia, detailing Campbell's political activities as a member of the Henrico County Democratic Committee and also containing information on the Democratic party at the local, state, and national levels. Papers also contain information on local, state, and national elections and election returns. Include papers relating to the Virginia Education Association and the National Education Association, as well as to the educational careers of Addison Campbell and Dawn S. Campbell.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
I: Henrico County Democratic Committee papers, 1965-1985.
II: District Democratic Parties papers, 1972-1984.
III: Virginia State Democratic Party papers, 1967-1992.
IV: Richmond Area Young Democrats papers, 1971-1980.
V: Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner papers, 1973-1984.
VI: National Democratic Party papers, 1964-1984.
VII: VEA/NEA records, 1972-1992.
VIII: Virginia State Board of Election papers, 1971-1980.
IX: Elections, 1965-1994.
X: Election returns, 1948-1981.
XI: General Politics, 1963-1993.
XII: Personal Papers, 1960-1981.
Contents List
- Series I: Henrico County Democratic Committee papers, 1965-1985., Extent: 11 boxes. (Box 1-11)
  Henrico County Democratic Committee papers, 1965-1985, covering the organization and operations of the county committee and party, membership, meetings and conventions, local campaigns, and relation to the state and national parties. Papers contain advertisements, agendas, ballots, budgets, bylaws, call lists, clippings, correspondence, declarations of candidacy, declarations of participant, forms, information cards, lists of members, meeting minutes and papers, motions, notes, policy statements, questionnaires, receipts, recommendations, reports, resolutions, tickets, and other papers.
  - Bylaws, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bylaws, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bylaws, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bylaws, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bylaws, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bylaws, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bylaws, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bylaws, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bylaws, no date (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Resolutions, recommendations, motions, etc., 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Resolutions, recommendations, motions, etc., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Resolutions, recommendations, motions, etc., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Resolutions, recommendations, motions, etc., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Resolutions, recommendations, motions, etc., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Resolutions, recommendations, motions, etc., 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Member, committee lists, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - member, committee lists, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Member, committee lists, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Member, committee lists, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Member, committee lists, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Member, committee lists, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Member, committee lists, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Member, committee lists, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Member, committee lists, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Member, committee lists, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Member, committee lists, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Member, committee lists, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Member, committee lists, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Member, committee lists, no date (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Meetings, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Meetings, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Meetings, January-February 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Meetings, April-December 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Meetings, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Meetings, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Meetings, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Meetings, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Meetings, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Meetings, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Meetings, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Meetings, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Meetings, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Meetings, 1981, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Attendance log, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Mass meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Mass meetings, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Mass meetings, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mass meetings, 17 May 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Mass meetings, 6 December 1975, declarations of participants--Brookland district (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Mass meetings, 6 December 1975, declarations of participants--Fairfield district (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Mass meetings, 6 December 1975, declarations of participants--Three Chopt district (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Mass meetings, 6 December 1975, declarations of participants--Tuckahoe district (A-Ha) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Mass meetings, 6 December 1975, declarations of participants--Tuckahoe district (He-M) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Mass meetings, 6 December 1975, declarations of participants--Tuckahoe district (P-Z) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Mass meetings, 6 December 1975, declarations of participaants--Varina district (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Mass meetings, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Mass meetings, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Mass meetings, 1977, declarations of participants--Brookland and Fairfield districts, blanks (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Mass meetings, 1977, declarations of participants--Three Chopt, Tuckahoe, and Varina districts (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Mass meetings, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Mass meetings, 1978, declarations of participants (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Mass meetings, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Mass meetings, 1979, declarations of participants--Brookland and Fairfield districts (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Mass meetings, 1979, declarations of participants--Three Chopt and Tuckahoe districts (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Mass meetings, 1979, declarations of participants--Varina district, blank forms (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Mass meetings, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Mass meetings, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Mass meetings, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Mass meetings, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - County convention, January-August 1971 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - County convention, September 1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - County convention, 1971, rules committee (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - County convention, 2 June 1973 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - County convention, 1973, correspondence (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - County convention, 1973, temporary rules committee (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - County convention, 1973, subcommittee on county convention procedures (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - County convention, 1973, delegate list by district (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - County convention, 1973, delegate lists (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - County convention, 1973, general papers (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - County convention, 7 June 1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - County convention, 1975, convention delegates lists (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - County convention, 1975, convention delegates candidates lists (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - County convention, 1975, ballots (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - County convention, 1975, correspondence (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - County convention, 1975, general papers (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - County convention, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - County convention, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, February-March 1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, April-May 1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, June-September 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, October-December, undated 1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, January 1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, February-June 1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, July-September 1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, April-September 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, October-December, no date 1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, January-June 1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, July-December no date 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, January-June 1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, July-December, no date 1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, April-December, no date 1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, January 1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, February-August 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Declarations of candidacy, committee member, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Declarations of candidacy, committee member, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Declarations of candidacy, committee member, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Declarations of candidacy, committee member, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Declarations of candidacy, committee member, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Declarations of candidacy, committee member, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Declarations of candidacy, committee member, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Declarations of candidacy, committee member, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Declarations of candidacy, committee member, no date (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Declarations of candidacy, county convention, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Declarations of candidacy, county convention, 1979, Brookland district (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Declarations of candidacy, county convention, 1979, Fairfield district (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Declarations of candidacy, county convention, no date, blank forms (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Declarations of candidacy, 3rd Congressional district convention, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Declarations of candidacy, 3rd Congressional district and state conventions, 1976, Brookland district (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Declarations of candidacy, 3rd Congressional district and state conventions, 1976, Fairfield district (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Declarations of candidacy, 3rd Congressional district and state conventions, 1976, Three Chopt district (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Declarations of candidacy, 3rd Congressional district and state conventions, 1976, Tuckahoe district (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Declarations of candidacy, 3rd Congressional district and state conventions, 1976, Varina district (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Declarations of candidacy, 3rd Congressional district and state conventions, 1976, blank forms (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Declarations of candidacy, state convention, 1978, uncomitted (A-F) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Declarations of candidacy, state convention, 1978, uncommitted (G-M) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Declarations of candidacy, state convention, 1978, uncommitted (O-W) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Declarations of candidacy, state convention, 1978, for Andrew Miller (A-G) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Declarations of candidacy, state convention, 1978, for Andrew Miller (H-Y) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Declarations of candidacy, state convention, 1978, for Conoly Phillips (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Declarations of candidacy, state convention, 1978, for Rufus Phillips (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Declarations of candidacy, state convention, 1978, for Clive DuVal, blanks (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Declarations of candidacy, state convention, 1978, financially incapable of paying filing fee (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Declarations of candidacy, House of Delegates, 1973, Ralph L. Bill Axselle (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Declarations of candidacy, House of Delegates, 1973, Robert B. Ball, Sr. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Declarations of candidacy, House of Delegates, 1973, David T. Walker (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Declarations of candidacy, Clerk of Henrico County Circuit Court, 1973, Margaret B. Baker (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Declarations of candidacy, Sheriff, 1973, Willard P. Bill Selph (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Declarations of candidacy, House of Delegates, 1975, Ralph L. Bill Axselle (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Declarations of candidacy, House of Delegates, 1975, Robert B. Ball, Sr. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Declarations of candidacy, House of Delegates, 1975, John G. Dankos (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Declarations of candidacy, House of Delegates, 1975, Robison Rob James (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Declarations of candidacy, state Senate, 1975, William F. Parkerson (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Declarations of candidacy, sheriff, 1975, Willard P. Bill Selph (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Declarations of candidacy, Clerk of Henrico County Circuit Court, 1975, Margaret B. Baker (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Declarations of candidacy, Henrico County board of supervisors, 1975, Donald R. Howren (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Declarations of candidacy, Henrico County board of supervisors, 1975, George W. Jinkins (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Declarations of candidacy, Henrico County board of supervisors, 1975, Charles M. Johnson (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Declarations of candidacy, Henrico County board of supervisors, 1975, Robert N. Johnson (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Declarations of candidacy, Henrico County board of supervisors, 1975, Anthony Mehfoud (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Declarations of candidacy, Henrico County board of supervisors, 1975, Eugene T. Rilee (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Declarations of candidacy, House of Delegates, 1977, Ralph L. Bill Axselle (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Declarations of candidacy, House of Delegates, 1977, Gerald L. Jerry Baliles (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Declarations of candidacy, House of Delegates, 1977, Robert B. Ball, Sr. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Declarations of candidacy, House of Delegates, 1977, Robison Rob James (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Declarations of candidacy, Commonwealth's Attorney, 1977, C. Rodney Chapman (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Declarations of candidacy, Commonwealth's Attorney, 1977, James Kulp (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Declarations of candidacy, House of Delegates, 1979, Ralph L. Bill Axselle (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Declarations of candidacy, House of Delegates, 1979, Gerald L. Jerry Baliles (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Declarations of candidacy, House of Delegates, 1979, Robert B. Ball, Sr. (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Declarations of candidacy, state Senate, 1979, William F. Parkerson (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Declarations of candidacy, Commonwealth's Attorney, 1979, Robert Bradenham (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Declarations of candidacy, no date, blank forms (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1975, Brookland district (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1975, Fairfield and Varina districts (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1975, Three Chopt district (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1975, Tuckahoe district (folder 1 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1975, Tuckahoe district (folder 2 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1975, Tuckahoe district (folder 3 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1977, Brookland and Fairfield districts (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1977, Three Chopt and Tuckahoe districts (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1978, delegates for U.S. Senator (uncommitted) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1978, delegates for U.S. Senator (Miller, C. Phillips, R. Phillips) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1978, miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Ballots and tickets, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Ballots and tickets, no date, convention--Brookland district (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Ballots and tickets, no date, convention--Fairfield district (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Ballots and tickets, no date, convention--Three Chopt District (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Ballots and tickets, no date, convention--Tuckahoe and Varina districts (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Ballots and tickets, no date (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Budgets, 1974-1985 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Receipts, 1973-1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Committee to Build a Stronger Democratic Party in Henrico, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Brookland District causus, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Committee surveys, ca. 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Committee surveys,, ca. 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Committee surveys, 1974, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Committee surveys, 1978-1980, no date (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Voter surveys, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Voter surveys, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Voter surveys, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Voter surveys, 1978 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Voter surveys, 1978 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Voter surveys, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Call lists, 1979, Brookland district (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Call lists, 1979, Fairfield district (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Call lists, 1979, Three Chopt district (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Call lists, 1979, Tuckahoe district (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Call lists, 1979, Varina district (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - List of delegates to state convention, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Polls and poll work, 1971-1981 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - numbers of voters, 1974-1981 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Workshop, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Workshop, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Democratic Fun Fest, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Fun Fest, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Democratic picnic, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - King's Dominion, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Use of school forms, 1975-1979 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Notes, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Notes, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Notes, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Notes, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Notes, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Notes, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Notes, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Notes, ca. 1975-1979 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Notes, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Notes, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Notes, no date (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - General papers, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - General papers, ca. 1965-1971 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - General papers, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - General papers, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - General papers, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - General papers, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - General papers, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - General papers, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - General papers, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - General papers, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - General papers, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - General papers, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - General papers, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - General papers, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - General papers, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - General papers, no date (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Information cards, no date (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Index cards with addresses, no date (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Series II: District Democratic Parties papers, 1972-1984., Extent: 1 box. (Box 12)
  District Democratic Parties papers, 1972-1984, containing papers relating to the 32nd District House of Delegates Democratic Committee, the 35th Legislative District Committee, and the 3rd Congressional Democratic Committee and Party in their activities and operations in political campaigns in their districts, and for their conventions. Series also contains papers relating to other counties' and cities' local Democratic committees and their operations. Papers consist of advertisements, correspondence, declarations of candidacy, lists, maps, meeting minutes, memorandums, reports, and other papers.
  - 32nd District House of Delegates Democratic Committee papers, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 35th Legislative District Democratic Committee papers, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee meetings, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee meetings, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee meetings, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee meetings, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee meetings, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee meetings, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee meetings, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee meetings, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee convention, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee convention, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee convention, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee convention, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee convention, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee convention, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee convention, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee correspondence, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee correspondence, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee correspondence, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee correspondence, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee correspondence, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee correspondence, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee correspondence, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee correspondence, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee member lists, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee declarations of candidacy, 1978, National Democratic Party Conference (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee general papers, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee general papers, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee general papers, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee general papers, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee general papers, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee general papers, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee general papers, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Third Congressional Democratic Committee general papers, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Series III: Virginia State Democratic Party papers, 1967-1992., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 13-16)
  Virginia State Democratic Party papers, 1967-1992, consisting of papers detailing the state Democratic party's organization, its conventions, and its campaigns to have its candidates elected to statewide (governor, lieutenant governor, attorney general) and national (senator, president) offices. Papers include agendas, ballots, booklets, certifications, clippings, correspondence, credentials, declarations of candidacy, lists, memorandums, notes, plans, reports, tickets, and other papers.
  - Convention, 1971, lists of Henrico County delegates (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Convention, 1971, papers (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Convention, 1972, lists of Henrico County delegates (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Convention, 1972, correspondence (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Convention, 1972, papers (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Convention, 1976, candidates for National Committee (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Convention, 1976, candidates for Democratic State Central Committee (Box 13, Folder 7)